AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- Boy scouts marching with flags. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref793)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Scouts; Streets/Roads; Uniforms
- School's taekwondo team marching in the street.10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref794)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sports; Sports teams; Streets/Roads; Students; Teachers
- Marching band. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref795)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Marching band; Music; Musical Instruments; Streets/Roads; Trees; Uniforms
- Girls marching with trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref796)
  Cars; Flags; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees; Trophies; Uniforms
- Boys marching with flags and trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref797)
  Boys; Buses; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees; Trophies; Uniforms
- Students marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref798)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees
- Boys marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref799)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref800)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees
- Students marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref801)
  Awards; Boys; Color Photography; Flags; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees; Walking
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref802)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees; Walking
- Students marching in the streets celebrating the 100th anniversary of Holy Family School. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref803)
  Boys; Buildings; Cameras; Cars; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Students; Walking; Women
- Man speaking in front of students. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref804)
  Boys; Color Photography; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Group portrait of the taekwondo team. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref805)
  Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports teams; Students; Trees
- Group portrait of students. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref806)
  Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Trees
- Taekwondo team performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref807)
  Boys; Color Photography; Crowds; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports; Sports teams; Students; Trees
- Group portrait of men and nuns.10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref808)
  Christians; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education
- Group of men smiling. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref809)
  Clothing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education
- Boy scouts performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref810)
  Boys; Color Photography; Crowds; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Scouts; Students; Tents
- Man speaking in microphone next to awards. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref811)
  Awards; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Trees; Women
- Boy scouts demonstrating skills in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref812)
  Boys; Color Photography; Crowds; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Scouts; Students
- Girls choir singing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref813)
  Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Singing; Students
- Group portrait of students. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref814)
  Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Man speaking in microphone. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref815)
  Awards; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education
- Crowd at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref816)
  Color Photography; Crowds; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Crowd at school awarding ceremony. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref817)
  Awards; Boys; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Camera man in front of crowd at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref818)
  Cameras; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Crowd at school event from above. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref819)
  Boys; Cameras; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees; Women
- Men in front of awards. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref820)
  Arabic Writing; Awards; Cameras; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Men presenting awards. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref821)
  Awards; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Man awarding students with medals. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref822)
  Awards; Boys; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Medals; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Man awarding a woman with a trophy. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref823)
  Awards; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Trophies; Women
- Girls performing at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref824)
  Color Photography; Crowds; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Performing arts; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Girls holding balloons during school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref825)
  Balloons; Cameras; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Girls performing at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref826)
  Color Photography; Crowds; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- Girls dancing at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref827)
  Awards; Color Photography; Crowds; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Performing arts; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Traditional Dress; Women's Clothing
- Men eating. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref828)
  Color Photography; Drinking; Eating; Flowers; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Men eating. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref829)
  Color Photography; Drinking; Eating; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Group portrait. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref830)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officers; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Uniforms
- Portrait of a man with two boys. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref831)
  Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education
- Group portrait in front of Egyptian flag. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref832)
  Boys; Color Photography; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officers; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Uniforms
- Man shaking hands with a boy. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref833)
  Boys; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref834)
  Boys; Clothing; Color Photography; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women; Women's Clothing
- Group portrait. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref835)
  Boys; Clothing; Color Photography; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Award ceremony. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref836)
  Awards; Boys; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- A teacher receiving an award during an honoring ceremony. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref837)
  Awards; Boys; Dresses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- A student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref838)
  Awards; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Trophies
- Students carrying flags during a school event.12.9 x 8.8 cm, 1982; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref839)
  Boys; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students
- Children performing in a school event.12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref840)
  Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Music; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Women
- A man taking a picture with his daughter(?). 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref841)
  Children; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education
- Student taking a photo with his trophy in a school event. 8.8 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref842)
  Adolescents; Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trophies
- Photo of a teacher shaking hands with an officer. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref843)
  Cigarettes; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Officers; Officials; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Uniforms
- An officer eating with teachers in school. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref844)
  Drinking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Food; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officers; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Uniforms; Women; Women's Clothing
- A teacher receiving an award during a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref845)
  Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Teacher receiving an award in a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref846)
  Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- A picture of school staff with officials. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref847)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Groups, Social; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- School staff in a meeting. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref848)
  Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Trophies; Women
- Boy scouts with the scoutmaster. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref849)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Scouts; Uniforms
- Students performing in a school event. 12.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref850)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony. 13.6 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref851)
  Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Group photo of the school's priests. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref852)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education
- Student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony in school. 12.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref853)
  Awards; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Woman taking pictures in a school event. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref854)
  Boys; Cameras; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Skirt; Students
- Group photo of school staff in a school event.12.3 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref855)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Group photo of school staff. 12 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref856)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- School staff with officials doing a salutation. 13.1 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref857)
  Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Uniforms
- Student receiving an award by an official. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref858)
  Awards; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Uniforms; Women
- Students performing in a school event. 13.1 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref859)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Vocal music
- School staff taking a picture with trophies in an honoring ceremony. 13.2 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref860)
  Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Trophies; Women
- Teachers receiving awards in an honoring ceremony. 11.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref861)
  Awards; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Trophies; Uniforms; Women
- Group photo of school staff. 13.1 x 8.9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref862)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Teacher and an official with two students. 12.4 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref863)
  Awards; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trophies; Uniforms
- Singer performing in a school event. 9 x 12.5 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref864)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Vocal music
- Group photo of school staff with an official. 13.3 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref865)
  Boys; Drinking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Food; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Uniforms; Women
- Group photo of school staff with a student. 13.1 x 8.7 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref866)
- School staff in a school event. 13.8 x 9 cm, 1 Dec 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref867)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Groups, Social; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education
- Children performing in a school event. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref868)
  Children; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Music; Photographic Prints; Radios; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Vocal music
- Group photo of teachers. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref869)
  Arabic Writing; Blackboard/Chalkboard; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Women
- Teachers eating. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref870)
  Arabic Writing; Blackboard/Chalkboard; Food; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Scoutmaster with boy scouts behind him. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref871)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Scouts; Uniforms
- Group school photo. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref872)
- Group photo of school staff. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref873)
  Coffee; Cupboards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Tea; Teachers
- School staff eating with officials. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref874)
  Coffee; Drinking; Eating; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Officials; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Tea; Teachers; Uniforms
- School staff. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref875)
  Awards; Cupboards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trophies
- Group portrait with school staff. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref876)
  Boys; Color Photography; Crowds; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School staff playing instruments. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref877)
  Boys; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Women shaking hands. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref878)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Egyptian clothing; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women; Women's Clothing
- Group portrait of women. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref879)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women; Women's Clothing